Should I care more than I do?
I am nihilistic lately, just like you
I am apathetic maybe I’m feeling blue
Oh I’m in love with all the wrong things
I cry more than I should
So I took a little pill and hey
I sort of felt like I would
Just float away aha
Should I try less than I do?
Someone once told me lately it’s all I ever do
Should I cry less than I do?
Someone once told me maybe this is all I’ll ever amount to
But I am like a knife
Like a french movie with subtitles
I am like a jackhammer
With nothing to lose
Nothing to lose aha
Nothing lose aha
But I am kind sometimes
I dance on high tables
I feel in all the right ways
Now that I am older
I say it like it is